fommy.co.in 2018-10-04

# Privacy policy - Fommy.co.in.

**Information We Gather Automatically**  
When you visit this website, certain non-personal identifying information is recorded automatically by the standard operation of our Internet servers in the United States. Information such as the type of browser being used, its operating system, and your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address (a number that your Internet service provider assigns to your computer whenever you surf the Internet), may be gathered in order to facilitate our online operations and to assure an efficient online experience for you. We may also use or share this information for security purposes to generate group statistics about our user community or as required by US law.

We may use your IP address or other automatically recorded information in cooperation with your Internet provider to identify you if it is necessary to contact you or to bring legal action against you because of violation of "Terms and Conditions" of using this website or for causing injury or interference (intentionally or unintentionally) with our company's rights or property with other users of this website or anyone else who could be harmed by your activities.

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**Information You Provide To Us**  
We may request personal and identifying information from you in a variety of contexts. For example, you may provide such data to us if you  
(1) complete an online registration form (ex: various sign-up forms for unlocking, registering for special offers or communications, registering for an account or responding to a survey);  
(2) fill out an order form to request information;  
(3) register to participate in any online interactive features we may offer;  
(4) purchase any products or services from us or another business within our family of companies.

In such cases, the personally identifying information we request may include your name, e-mail address, mailing address and zip code, mobile phone number, other phone number(s) and, where appropriate, a valid credit card number with expiration date (collectively, "Personal Information"). In addition, we may collect other non-personally identifying information such as your date of birth, gender, country of residence, language preference, hobbies and other information regarding your interaction with our site. Of course, you never have to answer any of the questions we ask you (nor choose to take advantages of the services offered on our site), but refusal to do so may limit the products or services we can offer or provide to you.

**Your Personal Information  
**Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our website, new services and special offers we think you may find valuable. The lists used to send you product and service offers are developed and managed under our traditional corporate standards designed to safeguard the security and privacy of our customers' personal information. As a customer, you may opt out by sending an e-mail to [ care@fommy.co.in](mailto:care@fommy.co.in).

Finally, without any specific approval from you, we may develop general aggregate data (ex: data that cannot be used to identify specific individuals) about our user community that is partly based on information about you. For example, hypothetically, you might be one of 1,000,000 customers between the ages of 25 and 35. We may share such aggregate statistics with Fommy affiliate companies without your consent.

**Legal Enforcement Purposes**  
We reserve the right to disclose your "Personal Information" as required by law or in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against you if you are violating the "Terms and Conditions" of use for this website or may be causing injury to or interference (intentionally or unintentionally) with our company's rights or property, other users of this website or anyone else who could be harmed by your activities.

**Safeguarding Your Personal Information**  
Fommy cares about the security of your 'Personal Information.' We follow generally accepted industry security standards to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use such 'Personal Information.' However, unfortunately, despite many advances in information security technology and procedures, no commercially deployed method of information transfer over the Internet or electronic data storage is known to be 100% secure. As a result, while we do strive to use modern and commercially reasonable means to protect your "Personal Information", we cannot guarantee the absolute security of that information during its transmission or its storage in our systems.

**Links to Other Sites**  
Our Privacy Policy does not apply to third party websites that may be accessible through the Fommy.co.in website. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of those third parties to learn how they collect and use information about you.

**How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or complaints about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [care@fommy.co.in](mailto:care@fommy.co.in). When we receive such inquiries about our Privacy Policy, we will use the "Personal Information" (such as your e-mail address) only to respond to your question or comment. However, if your question raises one or more issues that affect our promotional partners, we may also share your question with them in order to provide a response. 

**Changes in This Privacy Policy**   
We reserve the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time, so we encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we make changes which we consider material in our privacy practices, we will notify you in this space. We may also attempt to notify you of any such material changes to our privacy practices via e-mail or by placing a notice on our home page. If there are changes or additions to this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we collect online or offline, how we use it and what choices you have. Regardless of any changes we make to our Privacy Policy, we will only use your personal information in accordance with the version of the Privacy Policy in place at the time you provided your information, unless you later give your consent for us to do otherwise.  
**  
Acceptance of This Privacy Policy**  
By using this website, you consent to the collection and use of your "Personal Information" by Fommy.co.in in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on Feb 04, 2008.
